did you notice that Iman godi shut down
his marketing agency to start a SAS
business and Jordan Welch well he's all
about Drop Shipping but guess what he's
also diving into sass you see the
pattern here all the gurus on YouTube
and Tik Tok keep pushing dropshipping
and social media marketing agencies but
behind the scenes they're all switching
to SAS and there's a good reason for it
SAS is exploding right now and in 2025
it's way more profitable than the stuff
that most people are telling you to do
if you don't know what SAS is it stands
for software as a service here's how it
works you take a software that's already
built you put your own logo on it and
then you resell it as many times as you
want simple right but here's the kicker
you're still early there's only around
60,000 people worldwide that are
currently doing this getting in now is
like starting Drop Shipping back in 2010
it's a gold mine just waiting for you to
tap into and unlike all the other gurus
on this app I'm teaching you this for
free so if you want to learn how to get
started drop a follow let's go